reinventingaging.org 2016-06-19

# Privacy Policy · Reinventing Aging

**Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting reinventingaging.org, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

As a routine part of transacting business on the Website, Reinventing Aging, LLC may receive personally identifiable information from you such as, without any limitation, your name, address, email address, telephone number, email address, birth date, sex, weight and height, as well as information secured by Reinventing Aging’s service providers such as your credit card number, telephone number and address (individually and collectively the “Personal Information”). Reinventing Aging, LLC will NEVER share your personal information with third parties. 

In an effort to secure your trust and confidence, Reinventing Aging, LLC has taken various measures to protect your privacy as it relates to your transactions conducted on the Website.

By using the Website, you hereby agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy specifically incorporates Reinventing Aging LLC [Terms & Conditions](http://www.reinventingaging.org/terms-and-conditions/) and any terms not specifically defined herein shall have the same meanings as those terms are ascribed in the Terms & Conditions.

**Email Policy**

Our email marketing is permission based. If you received a mailing from us, our records indicate that (a) you have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

If you believe you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to support@reinventingaging.org for review.

**How can you stop receiving email from us?**

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the SafeUnsubscribe™ or Update Profile links at the end of any email.

**Cookies and other Technologies**

As is standard practice on many websites, we may set and access cookies, web beacons, Flash cookies, and other technologies on your computer. Please note that third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers, may also set and access cookies, web beacons, Flash cookies, and other technologies on your computer when you visit the Site. For more information, please [click here to see our cookie policy](http://www.reinventingaging.org/cookie-policy/).

**Private Information Security**

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, PayPal keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.

**3rd Party Disclosure**

Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

**Email Usage**

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to periodic company news, updates, and/or related product or service information, etc.

**Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Returns and Exchanges**

Not Satisfied? If for any reason you are not satisfied with your Reinventing Aging purchase we will be happy to provide a refund. [Click Here](http://www.reinventingaging.org/product-returns/) to read our our product return policy for instructions.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of reinventingaging.org then you may contact us at support@reinventingaging.org

**Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting reinventingaging.org, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

As a routine part of transacting business on the Website, Reinventing Aging, LLC may receive personally identifiable information from you such as, without any limitation, your name, address, email address, telephone number, email address, birth date, sex, weight and height, as well as information secured by Reinventing Aging’s service providers such as your credit card number, telephone number and address (individually and collectively the “Personal Information”). Reinventing Aging, LLC will NEVER share your personal information with third parties. 

In an effort to secure your trust and confidence, Reinventing Aging, LLC has taken various measures to protect your privacy as it relates to your transactions conducted on the Website.

By using the Website, you hereby agree, without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy specifically incorporates Reinventing Aging LLC [Terms & Conditions](http://www.reinventingaging.org/terms-and-conditions/) and any terms not specifically defined herein shall have the same meanings as those terms are ascribed in the Terms & Conditions.

**Email Policy**

Our email marketing is permission based. If you received a mailing from us, our records indicate that (a) you have expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information in the future (“opt-in”), or (b) you have registered or purchased or otherwise have an existing relationship with us. We respect your time and attention by controlling the frequency of our mailings.

If you believe you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to support@reinventingaging.org for review.

**How can you stop receiving email from us?**

Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the SafeUnsubscribe™ or Update Profile links at the end of any email.

**Cookies and other Technologies**

As is standard practice on many websites, we may set and access cookies, web beacons, Flash cookies, and other technologies on your computer. Please note that third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers, may also set and access cookies, web beacons, Flash cookies, and other technologies on your computer when you visit the Site. For more information, please [click here to see our cookie policy](http://www.reinventingaging.org/cookie-policy/).

**Private Information Security**

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, PayPal keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.

**3rd Party Disclosure**

Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.

**Email Usage**

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to periodic company news, updates, and/or related product or service information, etc.

**Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Returns and Exchanges**

Not Satisfied? If for any reason you are not satisfied with your Reinventing Aging purchase we will be happy to provide a refund. [Click Here](http://www.reinventingaging.org/product-returns/) to read our our product return policy for instructions.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of reinventingaging.org then you may contact us at support@reinventingaging.org

_________ ADVERTISEMENT _________
